you have no idea how good this
microphone is meet
the fifein ampligame a6v
[Music]
half of what makes a good video is a
good audio and today we're going to look
at the fifa ampligame a6v this is a usb
mic
that is created for
streamers and gamers it's very aesthetic
and
it is it produces great sound quality
without breaking the bank so stick
around to see what this microphone can
do
and shout out to fifa for sending this
microphone for me to review so make sure
to check them out
okay let's unbox this thing
so this is the box
overall the box is
very sturdy it's very professional
[Music]
protective foam
the literature that comes with it
it's pretty good it it's plastic but not
kind of like cheap plastic it's very
light but like i said it's not it's
still pretty good quality
it comes with a
smiley filter here and this is
detachable
just like that
and here is the microphone itself the
off and on button are up here and it is
touched it's not like a button it's just
touch
it has the shock mount
won't make that much rattle the gain
button is right here at the bottom
and it has this adjustable knob
here at the side
uh other things you get out of the box
is the tripod
and it is metal this is very sturdy i
like it
and the cable and i believe this is
sbc to usba okay let's set this up
so this
[Music]
and then you can adjust this however you
like
[Music]
this would just plug in at the back
and over and that's it it lights up
right away
it when it's lighted up it means that
it's working and you just press this
to
mute the microphone
and
and it stops the the light from going
the light
when there's no light it means that
the microphone is off
it's muted
this is a mic test for the rode wireless
go
this is a mic test
[Music]
for the native iphone
mic
this is a mic test
and this is a mic check for the fifein
ampligame a6v
this is a mic check
and this is a mic check for the fine
ampligame a6b
this is a mic check
this is a mic check for the fifein
ampligame a6v
game a6b
fee fine and the game a6v
fifein amphigame a6v
and v5 ampergame a6v
fifa and ampligame a6v
so final thoughts about this mic i
believe you can expect out of that out
of this fifa and ampligame a6v
um there is just some things that i wish
that were included with the mic
but that is just for personal preference
um
[Music]
one thing i wish the the change in the
design is that they put the
indicators on the side of the mic on
instead of underneath because there are
times where
i don't know if i'm
if i'm doing the gain if i'm recording
or
if
if i'm turning it right um
[Music]
however that's just perform personal
preference if you're doing live
streaming of course that's a little bit
different
uh
you know it's not uh it's not that big
of a deal because
you're you're hearing yourself as
you're hearing yourself when you're when
you're live streaming so
uh yeah but overall it's not that bad
but overall this mic is
is has great quality without breaking
that without breaking the bank without
spending too much money you can get this
podcast like quality under 40
so if you're on a podcast if you
a live streamer uh maybe if you record
if you're a
youtuber and you're recording videos
like these the this mic is very good
for voice overs and
as well as right now talking talking
videos
this mic is very aesthetic as well uh
perfect for any um any room and it'll
match you know if you have that uh basic
rgb lightroom uh
as most youtubers have uh this is
perfect vibe for that
so overall great looking mic and very
great job by fee fine
and that's it for today's video if you
enjoy this if you are looking for more
product reviews
check out my review on the road wireless
go or on my dji mini 2
down in the link below
see you in the next video
you